

Email: bongarabe28@gmail.com Contact No: 0939-222-4860 Address: 100-A Condrado Benitez Street, Cubao Quezon City

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Skilled Welder with proficiency in MIG, flux, stick welding, drill press, and metal fabrication. With 16 years of experience in layout, fabrication, installation, and repair of industrial equipment. Ability to expertly complete welding projects with efficiency and high-quality standards.

## **PERSONAL**

**Birthdate**: July 28, 1968 **Birthplace**: Quezon City

Sex: Male

Civil Status: Married Religion: Catholic Nationality: Filipino

Height: 5'10

**Language Spoken**: English, Tagalog and Nihongo

# **SKILLS**

- Expert in MIG
- Knowledgeable in Arc Welding
- Detail-Oriented
- Adaptability
- Time Management
- Forklift Operator

### **EDUCATION**

#### **Primary**

Pedro Tuazon Elementary School Quezon City (1975 to 1981)

# **Secondary**

Ponciano Bernardo High School Quezon City (1981 to 1985)

### **Tertiary**

Samson Technological Institute Practical Electricity (1986)

# **WORK HISTORY**

Las Islas Furniture Co. – Machine Operator Helper

Marrick Street Cainta, Rizal – 1986 to 1987

- Perfom operation of press to make the parts.
- Assisting others in processing, methods and work habits to maintain maximum efficiency
- Using various machines for cutting and punching parts

**Kubota Company** – Scaffolder and Painter Japan – 1990 to 1991

**Wex Laundry Co.** – Laundry Man Kita Toda, Japan – 1991 to 1993

### Forklift Operator Automatic – 1993 to 1994

- Operate forklifts and other machinery in warehouse.
- Load and unload freight trucks and sort of vegetable and fruits.

**Yanagida Steel Co.** – 5-15-40 Kawaguchi Nishi Kawaguchi Tel no. 0482-530102 Saitama Ken, Japan – 1994 to 2009

- Expert in using MIG, Arc, Metal Press Machine and Angle Bar.
- Maintained tools and equipment, ensuring proper function and minimizing repair cost.
- Efficiently organized and prepared tools and equipment prior to welding job, streamlining process and consistently completing projects.
- Heated, formed and dressed metal parts with hand tools, and arc welding equipment.
- Laid out, fitted and fabricated metal components.